[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]
Now that we've seen how regularization can play a role in the classification setting,
الآن بعد أن تعرفنا على دور التنظيم في إعداد التصنيف،
let's observe in our data set what happens to the boundaries as we introduce our
دعونا نلاحظ في مجموعة البيانات التي لدينا ما الذي يحدث إلى حدود القرار ونحن نقدم
regularization penalty.
عقوبة تنظيمية.
We're going to work with that Degree 20 features.
سنعمل مع ميزات الدرجة 20.
So feature discretion model with features of polynomial degrees 20,
نموذج التقدير الخاص مع ميزات متعددة الحدود من الدرجة 20،
which led to this technical term that I called the Crazy Decision Boundary.
الذي ينتج عنه هذا المصطلح الفني الذي أطلق عليه اسم "حدود القرار المعقدة".
And the parameters had very large magnitude,
حيث إن المتغيرات كبيرة جدا،
in fact it varied from minus 3,170 to 3,803, they were very big.
في الواقع، كانت تتراوح من سالب 3170 إلى 3803، أي أنها كبيرة جدًا.
Now we're going to take the same setting, same number of features, same features,
الآن سنأخذ نفس الإعداد، ونفس العدد من الميزات بل نفس الميزات،
same data, same everything but just vary the parameter lambda and
ونفس البيانات وجميع الأشياء، ونغير فقط المتغير "λ"
see what happens and here we're showing the results of doing exactly that.
لنرى ما سيحدث، وهنا نعرض نتائج القيام بذلك بالضبط.
When lamba is equal to zero, we get very large
فعندما تساوي λ الصفر، تصبح المعاملات كبيرة جدًا
coefficients when lamba is large like ten we get
وعندما تكون λ بقيمة كبيرة مثل عشرة نحصل على
good size coefficients, let's say smaller coefficients
معاملات بحجم معقول، ولنفترض أنها معاملات أصغر
Okay, and so for lambda equals zero,
وهكذا بالنسبة لλ تساوي الصفر،
we had that crazy decision boundary and for
كان لدينا حدود قرار معقدة
large lambdas, we have a nicer smoother boundary.
أما بالنسبة لλ بالقيم الكبيرة، فلدينا حدود أكثر سلاسة.
In fact, I trust that this boundary with lambda equal ten much more
بل في الواقع، أنا على ثقة من أن هذا الحد مع λ يساوي عشرة أكثر
than the one with lambda equals zero.
من مثيله في حالة λ تساوي صفرًا.
And the decision model of lambda equals ten looks a lot like that really beautiful
ونموذج القرار لλ الذي يساوي عشرة يشبه إلى حد كبير
one I got with the parabola, and fit my data really well but
هذا النموذج المتناسق الذي حصلت عليه من القطع المكافئ، كما أنه يناسب بياناتي جيدًا
here there are tons of more features and nevertheless, hiding a little bit of
وهنا يوجد العديد من الميزات، التي تطوي القليل من التنظيم
regularization help us get that really nice separating plane that I can trust.
تساعدنا على الحصول على هذا السطح الفاصل الذي أثق به.
We can also look to the coefficient parts, what happens to a coefficient
يمكننا أيضا أن ننظر إلى أجزاء المعامل، فما الذي يحدث للمعامل
as we increase the penalty lambda, so in the beginning,
ونحن نزيد العقوبة λ، لذلك في البداية،
when we have a unregularized problem this coefficient tends to be large.
عندما تكون لدينا مشكلة غير منتظمة، يميل هذا المعامل إلى أن يكون كبيرًا.
But as we increase lambda, they tend to become smaller and smaller and smaller and
ولكن مع زيادة λ، فإنها تميل إلى أن تصبح أصغر فأصغر
go to zero.
حتى تصل للصفر.
I've used the review data set, property review data set here and
لقد استخدمت مجموعة مراجعة البيانات، الخاصة بالملكية هنا
I picked a few words and fit a legislation model just using those words with
انتقيت بعض الكلمات ثم قمت باحتواء نموذج الانحدار اللوجستي فقط من خلال تلك الكلمات
different levels of regularization.
التي بها مستويات مختلفة من التنظيم.
So for example, the words that have positive coefficients tend to be
إذن، على سبيل المثال، الكلمات التي لها معاملات موجبة تميل إلى أن تكون
associated with positive aspects of reviews, while the ones with negative
مرتبطة بالجوانب الإيجابية للمراجعات، بينما مثيلتها ذات المعاملات السلبية
coefficients tend to be associated with negative aspects of reviews.
تميل إلى أن تكون مرتبطة بالجوانب السلبية للمراجعات.
What is the word in quotes that has the most positive weight?
ما هي الكلمة الموجودة بين علامتي الاقتباس التي لها الوزن الأكثر إيجابية؟
Well, if you look at the key here, you'll see the word that has the most positive
حسنًا، إذا نظرت إلى المفتاح هنا، سترى أن الكلمة الأكثر إيجابية
weight is actually the emoticon smiley face,
هي في الحقيقة الوجه التعبيري المبتسم،
well, the word that has most negative weight is another another
والكلمة التي لديها وزن سلبي أكثر هي
emoticon the sad face.
الوجه التعبيري الحزين.
And the beginning all these words have pretty large coefficients
وبداية كل هذه الكلمات لها معاملات كبيرة جدًا
except the words near zero, which are words like this
باستثناء الكلمات القريبة من الصفر، وهي كلمات مثل
and review, which are not associated with either positive things or negative things,
"المراجعة"، التي لا ترتبط بأشياء إيجابية أو سلبية،
although if the word review shows up it's slightly correlated with
على الرغم من أنه إذا تم عرض كلمة مراجعة، فستكون مرتبطة قليلًا
a negative review but in general, this coefficients much more than the others.
بالمراجعة السلبية، ولكن بشكل عام تلك المعاملات أكبر كثيرًا من المعاملات الأخرى
And as I increase the regularization lambda,
وكلما قمت بزيادة λ التنظيمية،
you see the coefficients can become smaller and smaller, and
ترى أن المعاملات قد تصبح أصغر فأصغر،
if I were to keep drawing this, they will eventually go to zero.
وإذا استمررت في رسم ذلك، فستصل في النهاية إلى الصفر.
And now, if I were to use cross validation to pick the best lambda,
والآن، إذا كنت سأستخدم التحقق المتقاطع لاختيار أفضل λ،
I'll get a result kind of around here, and I'm going to call that lambda star.
سوف أحصل على النتيجة تقريبًا هنا، وسأطلق عليها λ ستار.
And so that's what you do is cross validation, to find that point
وهذا ما تفعله هو التحقق من الصحة، لإيجاد النقطة
where it's fitting data pretty well, but it's not over-fitting it too much.
المناسبة جدًا للبيانات، ولكن ليس أكثر من اللازم.
And as a last point, I'm going to show you something that is pretty exciting.
وكنقطة أخيرة، سوف أريكم شيئًا شيقًا جدًا
It's really beautiful about regularization with regression.
ومتناسقًا جدًا، حول التنظيم مع الانحدار اللوجستي.
Regularization doesn't only address the crazy wiggly decision boundaries but
لا يقتصر التنظيم على حدود القرار المعقدة أو المتموجة فقط
addressing with those over-confidence problems that we saw
يل يتعامل مع مشاكل الثقة المفرطة التي رأيناها
with over-fitting regularization.
عند استخدام التنظيم في الاحتواء المبالغ.
So I'm taking the same coefficient, the same thing that I've learned.
لذلك آخذ نفس المعامل، ونفس الشيء الذي تعلمته.
The lambda is increasing, the range of coefficients is decreasing,
بتزايد قيمة λ، يتناقص نطاق المعامِلات،
they're getting smaller but I'm talking the bottom here.
وتصبح اصغر لكنني أشير إلى الجزء الأسفل هنا.
The actual decision boundaries that we learned and
حدود القرار الفعلية التي تعلمناها
the notion of uncertainty on their data.
ومفهوم عدم اليقين من البيانات.
So if lambda is equal to zero we have this highly over confident predictions.
لذلك إذا كانت λ تساوي الصفر، فستصبح التوقعات موثوقة للغاية.
If lambda is a one, not only do I get a more natural kind of parabola like
وإذا افترضنا أن λ واحد، فأنا لا أحصل فقط على النوع الطبيعي من حدود القرار
decision boundary even though I'm using Degree 20 features,
المتشابهة مع القطع المكافئ، بالرغم من أنني استخدم الميزات من الدرجة 20،
polynomial degree 20 is features.
أو ميزات كثيرات الحدود من الدرجة 20.
I get a very natural certainty region.
بل أحصل على منطقة بنسبة يقين كبيرة.
So the region why I don't know if it's positive or
إذن، فالمنطقة التي لا أعرف هل هي إيجابية
negative is really those points in the boundary which kind of between
أم سلبية، تتمثل في النقاط داخل الحدود تقريبًا بين
those clusters of positive points and the clusters of negative points.
هذه المجموعات من النقاط الإيجابية وتلك المجموعات من النقاط السلبية.
And you get this kind of beautiful smooth transition.
لتحصل على هذا الانتقال السلس المتناسق نوعًا ما.
So by introducing regularization, we've now addressed those two fundamental
لذلك من خلال تقديم مفهوم التنظيم، قمنا الآن بتناول تلك المشكلتين الأساسيتين
problems where over-fitting comes in in logistic aggression.
حيث يظهر الاحتواء المبالغ مع الانحدار اللوجستي.
[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]